palms.com 2018-06-14

# Privacy Policy

###  Intro

We’re great at keeping secrets and strive to keep your personal information confidential. By ensuring that you’re aware of and understand Palms Website Privacy Policy, we can provide you with better service.

Below are the privacy policies that govern the official websites for Palms Casino Resort, namely palms.com, studioatthepalms.com, palmsplace.com and others (collectively, the “Website”). Please take a moment to see how we collect and use your personal information.

###  General

You can visit and enjoy our Website without disclosing any personal information about yourself. However, we offer some special services, and for these services to work properly you will need to share with us certain personal information about yourself. The personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to, first and last name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number (e.g., home, work, mobile and/or fax), gender, social security number, birth date and other personal information you choose to provide to us, including personal information concerning a third party which you are authorized to proved to us. We may also collect other personal information that will be identified on the applicable page(s) of the Website. If you submit any personal information to us, or to our third party service providers acting on our behalf, you can be assured that we will not sell, lease, or share your personal information about yourself. The personal information we collect may include, but is not limited to, first and last name, street address, e-mail address, telephone number (e.g., home, work, mobile and/or fax), gender, social security number, birth date and other personal information you choose to provide to us, including personal information concerning a third party which you are authorized to proved to us. We may also collect other personal information that will be identified on the applicable page(s) of the Website. If you submit any personal information to us, or to our third party service providers acting on our behalf, you can be assured that we will not sell, lease, or share your personal information with or to anyone else, except as follows: (1) to our third party service providers, and only so that they may help us provide the services you’ve requested and in certain circumstances to provide you with special offers and discounts; (2) upon notice posted on an applicable location of our Website where we collect your personal information for an economic transaction and notify you that we will be sharing such information with a third party where such third party is clearly identified; and (3) on occasion, we may offer a special promotion (such as a sweepstakes, contest, or other discount or giveaway) on the Website in conjunction with us or a third party service provider, sponsor or promotional partner and share your information with that sponsor or promotional partner so that either of us can send you other information and special promotions it offers but only if you give us permission to do so.

###  Club Palms

Every visitor is invited to sign up for a Club Palms Account, through which you can earn cash awards, complimentary meals, and other exciting special offers. In order to sign up for this service, you will be asked to provide personal information including your name, address, gender, date of birth, your social security number and other information. The Palms may combine this information with any other data we have collected about you using our offline resources. The Palms will use this information for future purposes, for example we may send you e-mails with special offers and promotions. You may opt-out of receiving these correspondences from us by either calling customer service at 1-866-942-7777, or by following the opt-out procedures detailed in the correspondence

###  Online Reservations

Visitors to the Website have the ability to search for rates and availability at Palms without ever providing any personal information. However, once you have decided on an available reservation, you will be asked to provide personal information. This will include your name, address, and other contact information, as well a credit card number, billing address, and the card’s expiration date. The credit card number will be used solely to secure your reservation as detailed in the reservation process. Palms will create a private account for you based on the information you have provided as part of the reservation process. If you need to access and/or modify any information in this account, including your travel plans, you may contact Palms’ reservation center toll free at 1-866-725-6773. Palms will also combine this information with any other data we have collected about you using our offline resources.

Palms takes reasonable steps to ensure that the reservations page on the Website is secure. For more information about our secure certificates, please click on the gold “Verisign” seal located on each reservations page. For more information about our current security methods, please see the “Our Security Practices” section below.

###  Information Collection

We may use automatic methods such as cookies (small amounts of data, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier that is sent to your browser from a Website’s computers and stored on your computer’s hard drive) and single-pixel GIF images alone or in combination with personally identifiable information you choose to provide us, to make our Website work better, to understand Website usage and trends, deliver a more personalized experience and to improve our content and offerings. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze using such methods include, without limitation, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; e-mail address; type and version, operating system, and platform; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, on, and from our Website, including date and time; cookie information; pages you viewed or searched for; and pictures you viewed. We may also use software tools to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to accept or reject cookies. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you may not be able to take advantage of certain services on our Website.

We do not transfer cookies associated with our Website to any other company, nor do we authorize any other company to access the cookies we have placed on your computer’s hard drive. We may allow other companies that are presenting advertisements or providing services on our pages to set and access cookies on your computer. Those companies’ use of cookies will be covered by their own privacy policies, not ours.

We do not install any spyware or adware in connection with our Website, or distribute any commercial message, or authorize any third party to distribute any commercial message, by means of spyware or adware. “Spyware” or “adware” is any software which has been downloaded to and/or installed on an Internet user’s computer, without the user’s actual consent, and facilitates the distribution of any commercial message to the user. If you feel you may have spyware from another company installed on your machine, there are various anti-spyware/adware software applications available on the Internet to identify if this has occurred.

###  Demographic Information

We may share aggregated demographic information with third parties, but this information is not linked to any personal information that can identify you or another individual person. Therefore, no personal information is disclosed in this manner.

###  Business Transfers

As time passes, Palms may be sold along with its assets, or other transactions may occur in which customer information is one of the business assets transferred. In such a case, the customer information which we have gathered may be one of the business assets we transfer.

###  Disclosure for Legal Purposes

The law requires that we may be required to share your personal information and non-personal information (see “Cookies” section above for examples of non-personal information) pursuant to judicial or governmental subpoenas, warrants or orders. If we are required to do so, we will, of course, obey the law. In addition, notwithstanding any term to the contrary in this Privacy Policy, we reserve the right to use and disclose share your personal and non-personal information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of this Website’s Terms of Use, or as otherwise required by law.

### Security Practices

In certain areas, we use industry-standard SSL encryption to protect data transmissions.

###  Reviewing Personal Information

Except as otherwise stated, the Website does not offer a way for you to review the personal information you provided in applying for a Club Palms account, or otherwise. If you want to review this information, call Palms Customer Service at 866-942-7777. If you want to revise the personal information you provided in applying for a Club Palms account and whether you want to continue to receive special offers from us, go to the “Gaming” menu bar, click on “Club Palms” and fill out a new application with the revised information. If you want to close your account with us and have us delete the personal information in it (except for information that we keep for record-keeping purposes), you should contact the Palms Customer Service at 866-942-7777.

###  Choice

Certain information forms on our website contain a box for you to indicate whether or not you consent to receive special offers and promotions from us. Unless you give us your consent to use your personal information for these purposes, we and our partners will only use it to complete the transaction or provide the service or product you have requested. If you indicate that you consent to receive communications or solicitations but you later change your mind, you should contact the Palms Customer Service at 866-942-7777 or follow the opt-out procedures detailed in the communication.

###  Links

Our Website contains links to other sites owned or operated by the Palms, affiliates and websites operated by unrelated third parties. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when your leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of every website that collects personally identifiable information from you. The Privacy Policy applies only to this Website.

###  Children and Privacy

Palms Websites do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13. The Palms does not knowingly solicit personal information from children, send them requests for personal information or distribute their personal information to third parties without parental consent.

###  Notification of Changes

If we decide to make an important change to our Privacy Policy, we will post a notification and link on our homepage so that you can review the updated policy. If at any point we wish to use your personal information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify you by means of an e-mail and give you the opportunity to indicate whether you consent to the proposed use. We encourage you to review the privacy policy regularly for any changes.

###  Entertainment

Artists appearing or performing at the Pearl Concert Theater have creative control over their own shows. The views expressed therein do not reflect those of Palms Casino Resort.
